(Leonard:)your stuff back into your
account and then be on our way.
(Leonard:)No one's bat'lething anybody.
(Sheldon:)So my blade shall not
taste blood tonight?
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)Well, now I just feel silly
holding it.
(Leonard:)Come on.
(Sheldon:)Can I at least
kick down the door?
(Leonard:)You're welcome to try, but
the other day, it took you
(Leonard:)15 minutes to get
into a FedEx box.
(doorbell rings)
MAN:
Who is it?
(Sheldon:)Your doom!
Don't say "your doom."
(Raj:)Who opens the door
for their doom?
(Sheldon:)Good point.
(Sheldon:)Basket of puppies.
(Policeman:)What?
(Leonard:)Uh...
(Leonard:)Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Are you Todd Zarnecki?
(Todd:)Yeah. Who are you?
(Sheldon:)I am Sheldor of Azeroth.
(Sheldon:)I want my things back.
(Todd:)I don't think so.
(Todd:)Let me see that.
(Sheldon:)Careful.
That's a collectible.